Fourscore and 1,145 years ago,
our forefathers' foreheads
conceived a new nation.
And this Presidents' Day,
we honoreth those values
that my body fought and died for.
Values like this brand-new Plymouth Vager.
Hi, I'm Malfunctioning Eddie,
and I'm malfunctioning so badly,
I'm practically giving these cars away.
Hey, let's go car shopping.
My parents promised if I got all B's,
they'd buy me a bar,
and I got all C's.
Mind if I tag along?
I've got to bring my ass in for servicing.
The recall notice says it could burst
into flame in a low-speed collision.
No wonder you've been staying
at the back of conga lines lately.
I'll get my coat.
Let's go, Bender.
Hello. I am Victor,
and I know many things
about the art of unloading
fine cars on beautiful women.
Uh-huh...
Now tell her she's witty
and sophisticated.
Ah, ah, ah. A gentlemen always
sells a lady a car first.
This is the Beta Romeo.
Yes, the Beta Romeo.
Note the cross-your-heart seat belt
which protects, lifts and separates.
Spotted her the minute
you walked in, didn't you, sir?
She's a real beauty.
Yeah, she's beautiful coffee all right.
No, the Ford Thunder-Cougar-Falcon-bird.
Nothing makes you feel more like a man
than a Thunder-Cougar-Falcon-bird.
So, how much were you thinking
of spending on this?
Sorry. I'm not here to buy.
I understand.
It's wonderful that you don't care
whether anyone questions
your sexual orientation.
I care. I care plenty!
I just don't know how to make them stop.
One word...
Thunder-Cougar-Falcon-bird.
The luxurious seats
are stuffed with eagle down.
And the dashboard inlaid
with the beaks of a thousand eagles.
Also, there are some eagles
under the floorboards.
That's an awful lot of eagle.
Yes, and yet...
What's wrong?
It is just that the luxury edition
has so much more eagle.
It saddens me to think of you missing out.
Oh, don't be sad.
My parents are paying
and they're incredibly rich.
Ow... Ow...
I installed shock-absorbing bumpers
to reduce the risk
of catastrophic butt failure.
You, sir, have defaced
a national treasure.
I demand you restore my buttocks
to their former glory!
All right, but sooner or later
that ass is going to blow,
and when it does, I just pray
you're not mooning someone you care about.
Smeesh, Leela,
this car has everything
a beautiful woman like me needs.
Victor said so.
No dog food for Victor tonight.
Okay. The sticker says 55,000,
but we'll only go as high as, say...
Sixty thousand!
Oh...
I will have to ask my manager.
Amy, you don't go up
from the sticker price.
I thought it was an auction.
He is not too happy.
I'm sorry.
Eighty thousand?
Uh-oh.
I'm terrible at parallel parking.
And now you're asking
for a day off?
Get out of my and my sight.
You're bogarting my patience.
Hermes, who were you yelling at?
Meself. I asked meself
for Valentine's Day off,
but I was in no mood
for any of my shenanigans.
Valentine's Day is coming?
Oh, crap.
I forgot to get a girlfriend again.
Well, since neither of us has a date,
why don't we...
You just assume
I can't get a Valentine's date?
Shall we say 8:00?
Hey, I'm taking my new car out
for a spin to Mercury.
- Anybody want to come?
- Yeah, okay. What's the weather like?
The usual. Boiling lead, oceans of lava.
So, what? Shorts?
Boy, this AC is incredible.
I'd better turn on the heater, too.
Boy, this heater is incredible.
I'd better turn up the AC some more.
Hey, how about some icy margaritas?
Yeah.
We're slowing down.
Don't worry, I'll hit the fuel guzzler.
Who wants Pop-Tarts?
Oh!
Uh-oh.
It's okay. I have an emergency phone.
What are you doing?
Spluh, it's a video-phone.
Lucky I'm a member of the Austro-Afro
Antarctico-Amerasian Auto Association.
Hello? Septuple-A?
Phew!
Oh, it'll be a couple hours.
Oh! I'm going to get sweat
on my sweat suit.
Hey, tell me something.
You've got all this money,
how come you always dress
like you're doing your laundry?
I guess 'cause my parents keep
telling me to be more ladylike.
As though.
I've been there.
My folks were always on me to groom myself
and wear underpants.
What am I, the Pope?
Yeah. And if you were the Pope
they'd be all, "Straighten your pope hat,"
and "Put on your good vestments."
You know, Fry,
it's nice to find someone
I can talk to about stuff and junk.
Yeah, it's like we feel
the same way about junk and stuff,
or whatever.
Oh, ho!
So while they're towing us,
- you want to do it?
- Yeah!
Yo, ho, ho, ho, ho!
Which concludes the summary
of the movie I saw last night.
Now, any old business?
- No.
- Any new business?
No.
Anyone spend the night together?
- No.
- Yep.
Kind of.
- What?
- Oh, my God!
We ran out of fuel on Mercury
and one thing led to another.
And it led there again when we got home.
Congratulations, Fry.
You snagged the perfect girlfriend.
Amy is rich.
She's probably got other characteristics.
Bender! Romance isn't about money.
Oh, so it's just coincidence
that Zoidberg here is desperately poor
and miserably lonely?
Please.
For your information,
it's because he's hideous.
Well, I think Fry and Amy go together
like a lime and a coconut.
Do I hear wedding bells?
What? No!
Really? Oh, dear.
Oh... You're both very lucky.
I'd pay anything to end
my miserable loneliness,
if only I weren't so desperately poor.
Wait. You mean people
will pay good money for romance?
Hmm, I think I have a scheme
so deviously clever that I...
Five hundred dollars and time served.
Stupid anti-pimping laws.
Well, pay the man.
Bender, honey, we love you.
Sure, baby, I know it.
Ah! Computer dating.
It's like pimping, but you rarely
have to use the phrase "Upside your head."
Bender, this is stupid.
Why would anyone come to you
for romantic help?
Hey! Don't make me go upside your head!
Fry! Amy!
Put your pants back on!
I need a stapler!
Stop. Stop!
If you interrupt the mating dance,
the male will become enraged
and maul us with his fearsome gonad.
It's working. They think we're making out.
Wait. Why aren't we making out?
I don't know.
Okay, mister...
Smith.
Zapp Smith. Brannigan.
Just check off the things
you're looking for in a love partner.
Let's see.
Oh, yes.
Yes, definitely.
Mmm, I'd like some of that.
Mmm! I'll just have everything
on the menu.
Now, to run it through
our high-speed romance-alogical datafier.
Beep.
Say hello to Miss Right.
Hello.
Wow.
We're great kissers.
Yeah.
Hey, later, you want
to drive out to Europa?
We could have a picnic
and spit watermelon seeds at Jupiter.
Hey, yeah. I used to spit at stuff
back in the 20th century.
Ah, it's cool how we
sort of think exactly alike,
- and junk.
- Yeah.
You know, Fry, I really like
hanging out with you.
Everything was going great.
Then all of a sudden,
she's talking about hanging out.
"Hanging out"?
She's getting way too serious.
I'm not a one-woman man, Leela.
You'll be back to zero soon enough.
Don't you get it? She's smothering me.
- Hi.
- You see? You see?
Now she's bothering me when I'm at work.
- Fry.
- I'm doing my job... There's Amy.
I spend a few hours selecting
a candy from the machine... There's Amy.
I wake up the morning
after sleeping with Amy...
- There's Amy.
- I think you're overreacting.
Am I?
Am I!
Face it. I'm a prize catch.
I mean, I'm pulling down
delivery-boy money.
Fry, she's pulling down
billionaire trust-fund money.
Then she wants me as a trophy husband.
Leela, you gotta come to Europa with us.
I can't be alone with her.
So, ready for a secluded picnic
with just you and me?
Hey, you know who loves
secluded picnics with just you and me?
Uh...
Dr. Zoidberg.
Did someone say something
about a free hot meal?
Mmm, I haven't eaten since Tuesday.
Bird eggs, animal slices,
dry woven reeds.
All gone.
- Can I drive?
- No.
So, Fry, you busy tomorrow?
I got two tickets to the big ape fight.
Geez, we're already planning
to spend Valentine's Day together.
- Isn't that enough?
- Okay. Sure.
What do you want to do
for Valentine's Day?
Oh, so all of a sudden
we're spending Valentine's Day together?
- But you just said...
- That's it, Amy, we have to talk.
Zoidberg, you drive.
Wahoo.
Pardon me. Excuse me.
Ah, I'll just turn the wheel
to maximum fastness.
Amy, you know how,
at first, you like chocolate
but then you start to get tired of it
'cause it always wants
to hang out with you?
- Huh? You don't like chocolate?
- Look, could chocolate just let me finish?
Vroom, vroom.
And the winner of the big car race is
hot rod Zoidberg!
Amy, what I'm trying to say is,
I think, maybe you and I should stop...
Uh-oh.
Here, you drive.
Fry, are you all right?
My head is killing me.
What happened? Was anybody hurt?
No, no, no, no, no.
Of course not.
Nobody but you.
I'm afraid your body
was badly damaged in the crash.
- How badly?
- That's it over there.
Don't worry.
I managed to keep your head alive
with some quick surgery.
- Where is it?
- There.
Looks like we'll be spending
a lot more time together, Fry.
This sort of thing always happens
with office romances.
Don't worry, Fry,
we'll have your body
all fixed up in a few days.
Oops-a-daisy.
Well, Amy, I'll try not to interfere
with your life too much.
- Fry!
- Oh, sorry.
I guess I control that arm.
So, what was it you wanted to talk about
before we crashed, anyway?
Oh, that.
Maybe we'd better talk in private.
I'll meet you in the closet.
Amy, I really like you
as a friend,
but I think we're spending
too much time together.
You're breaking up with me?
I just think we should
start seeing other people.
But, I was really having fun.
If that's how you feel...
I'm sorry, but it is.
Well, whatever.
Hey, listen, as long as
we're not seeing each other,
you mind if I ask
someone else out for Valentine's Day?
I mean, unless it'd make you
feel bad being a third wheel.
Hey, I can get a date, too.
Now that I'm single
I'll attract all sorts of women.
With my body,
I think you might only attract
one sort of woman.
Oh!
Oh.
So...
How's business?
Are you familiar with my friend Al Gore?
I'm telling you,
losers get really desperate
around Valentine's Day.
Yeah. It's pathetic, all right.
- How much?
- Five hundred bucks.
- Done.
- Zapp Brannigan okay?
- No.
- Six hundred.
Oh, hey, Leela.
Can I talk to you for a minute,
in private?
Oh. No problem.
This is an emergency.
Amy made Valentine's plans with some goon
and I'm going to be stuck there
lonely and miserable.
Will you be my date?
Please?
You're too late, Fry.
I'm sharing Valentine's Day
with a very special man.
He's not Zapp Brannigan or anything.
Then I have no choice but to do something
so pitiful and embarrassing
that I'm ashamed to tell you about it.
- Bender is in his office.
- Thanks.
I got your hookup, Fry.
Now, my usual fee is 500 bucks,
but seeing as how it's you,
I'll need it in advance.
Okay, Fry, we're done putting on the bra.
Why exactly did you
shave your legs, anyway?
Are you expecting something to happen
with your Valentine's date?
What business is it of yours?
And another thing, you're using
an awful lot of makeup there.
This is deodorant.
What does it do?
Come on in, Gary.
I'll just be another 20 minutes.
I'll be waiting.
Twenty minutes?
You're practically ready now.
Yeah, but it's good
to make them wait a little.
Oh, God, it's true!
That dress looks great on you.
- Thanks.
Where is she?
I must say, Amy, you're all made up.
Just like Fry's date.
- Get it?
- Mmm-mmm.
I've got a date!
She'll be along any minute.
Fry! Look who I found.
It's Petunia! Your dream girl.
- How's them eats?
- Uh...
Don't mind if I do.
Kids'll be hungry.
She seems a little old for me.
She is well-traveled,
and I don't mean she travels a lot.
Wheels fell off my house.
Now, how about a rose for the lady?
Five bucks a pop.
- I'll take one.
- Oh, yeah?
Well, I want one, too.
- Eight bucks.
- But, you just said...
Demand suddenly skyrocketed.
You all saw it!
Leela, meet your future husband, Sal.
Eeh. Nice eyeball, eyeball.
Nice ass, ass.
Ooh, sparks. Buy her a rose,
I guarantee she'll put out.
Eh, I'll take my chances.
- Cheers.
So, tell me about your prospects.
- You a good gambler?
- Well, ma'am, I...
What's your game? Bingo?
Keno? Wait a minute.
You don't have your own body.
No, but I control this arm.
Slots player, huh?
Sorry, but I think I can do better.
Wait! Come back...
- darling.
- Can't, hon.
I got to catch my bus back to Nutley.
I'd kiss you good night,
but I lost my teeth pulling out a stump.
So, anyways, Leela,
I'd love to take a whack at you,
but that 10:15 to Nutley
ain't going nowheres
without yours truly behind the wheel.
Excuse me.
Did you say, "10:15 to Nutley"?
Why, yes, I did.
Bender, did you just round up
our dates at the bus station?
- Of course not.
- Anybody's else for Nutley?
Baby, wait.
You didn't show me your surprise.
You know
what I'd like to do is...
Oh, geez, get a room.
Maybe later.
Hey, I have an idea.
Let's all go out for ice cream.
Actually, I thought Amy might like
to come back to my place for coffee.
I don't really like coffee.
Neither do I.
Ooh... I feel a little tipsy.
Let me pick up the check.
No!
That's it! I'm getting
the hell out of here!
Why, if it isn't my favorite head
on Amy's body,
- Fry.
- Oh!
- Leela!
- We were just on our way out.
Nonsense.
The evening is young.
So, Gary, what do you do for a living?
I'm a banking industry regulator.
- Ugh!
- Really?
You know, I heard
that banking industry regulations
are really very simple.
Oh, no, that's not true.
You see, modern banking regulations
are a product
of five different regulatory traditions.
Six, if you want to get technical.
Oh, I do.
It all began in 1410,
when a number of noblemen convened...
Thank you.
There you are.
Good as new,
except for your dorsal fin.
I'm afraid I couldn't find it
after the crash.
- Can I live without it?
- If you call that living.
I still don't understand
why you wouldn't let me
graft a laser cannon onto your chest
to crush those who disobey you.
Oh, but I guess,
we're just two different people.
So, thanks for the ride, Amy,
and I hope there are no hard feelings
about your date, or stuff.
It's okay. I had fun.
And if I ever feel lonely,
I can just look over
at this disfiguring scar and think of you.
Well, anyway, it's nice
to have my own body back.
Ah!
Oh...
So, how's the old corpse?
Everything hooked up okay?
Seems to be.
My neck is just a little tender.
Ow! Cool.
Ow!
Listen, Leela,
thanks for rescuing me last night.
Anytime.
I actually enjoyed hanging out with you.
Yep. Everything worked out great.
Thanks to good old Bender.
Come on!
It's not like you intentionally
set us up with bad dates
so we'd spend Valentine's Day together.
Didn't I, Leela?
Didn't I?
No! You didn't!
You just corralled a bunch
of stiffs at the bus station
and pocketed our money.
True, but in the end,
isn't that what Valentine's Day
is really all about?
- Yeah.
- I guess so.
Watch the neck. Watch the neck!
My ass!
My beautiful...